Like this.
このように
Do you want to touch your hand?
あ なた の手を触りたいの?
It's like this.
こんな感じだよ
If I say Iboji, am I not Iboji?
私 が イボジと言うと、私はイボジではないの?
I
私
I'll show you this later.
は これを後で見せるよ
Let me dig into your pants more!
もっとパンツを食い込ませて!
Ah, I feel like I just touched it.
あ、ちょっと触っちゃった気持ち
Like this?
こんな感じ?
Are you wet?
濡れてますか?
I'm getting a little wet.
ちょっと濡れてきちゃった
I won't throw it away to my pussy.
オナに捨てないよ
Take off your pants and cover it with your fingers.
パンツ脱いで指で隠して
Not yet.
まだダメ
Please lift your toes.
つま先ドアップお願い
Toes.
つま先
Can you see it?
見えるかな?
Before I knew it, I had over 5,000 people and was number 1.
いつの間に5千人超えて1位だよ
Thank you so much.
本当ありがとう
Chikubi?
チクビ?
Chikubi, is that what you want to see?
チクビ、そんな見たいの?
It's chikubi.
チクビだよ
It's shaved.
パイパンだよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Shaved pussy is the worst.
パイパンは最悪だわ
Sorry.
ごめんね
She looks like Naru-chan Yamada.
山田なるちゃんに似てるね
I don't know?
だあれわかんない?
I can only show you a little bit of my pussy.
マンコはちょっとしか見せれないよ
Kupa is no good.
クパはダメ
Do you have calluses all over the soles of your feet?
足の裏いっぱいタコあるの?
I might have stood up a little.
チ ク ビちょっと立ってきちゃったかも
Chi fired up.
チ クビアップ
What do you think?
どうですか?
like?
好き?
Chikubi.
チクビ
Around 20 years old?
20歳くらい?
I'm 20 years old.
20歳だよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Slam from cross-eyed.
寄り目からのスラムして
Something like this?
こういうこと?
difficult.
難しい
What does a pussy up look like?
マンコアップはこんな感じ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Are your armpits smooth too?
脇もツルツル?
It's smooth.
ツルツルです
Please show your side and cross your eyes.
脇見せて寄り目してください
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Close your eyes
寄 り目して
please.
ください
I don't know.
む ずい
I'm getting horny.
ムラムラしちゃうね
I want to see Chikubi.
チクビ見たい
Show me that with the M letter.
M字であんなる見せ
Does it look like that?
あ んなる見えるかな?
Annaru.
あんなる
I want to put it out already.
もう出したいです
It's no good if I take it out.
だめだよ出したら
It's still early, isn't it?
まだ早いでしょ
Let's do something more erotic.
もっとエロいことしよう
Okay.
よ いしょ
People are long.
人長いね
Is that so?
そうかな?
Show me your tsundoi.
ツンドイ見せて
This is what Tsundoi looks like.
ツンドイはこんなです
I think I'll do something like this.
ちょっとこんなにしちゃおうかな
One positive centrifuge is visible.
片方の正遠心が見えています
It's really interesting.
めっちゃ面白い
I think I'll pay to go once I go.
一回行ったら有料行こうかなって思います
I'll blow the sun
日を吹くよ
Can you pee for me for a fee?
有料でおしっこしてくれませんか?
I will.
するよ
This was also the last time I peed.
この間も最後におしっこしたんでね
I want to go, so I'll pay to go.
行きたいから有料行こうと思います
Let's continue further.
もっと続きしよう
I fell.
落ちちゃった
I'll be waiting.
待ってます
Please come.
来てね
I would be happy if you could ponytail it later.
後でポニーテしてくれると嬉しい
Okay, later.
いいよ後ですよ
Today is?
今日は?
What is that?
あれは?
Will you wear your neck today?
今日も首はつける?
picture?
え?
someone.
誰か
Do you have a collar?
首輪はいるか?
After all, it's Minami Gato.
やっぱりがとおみなみ
you're welcome.
どういたしまして
I like doing it over my pants like this at first.
最初こうやってパンツの上からやるの好きなんだよね
I just went there again.
さっきもう一回行っちゃったんだけど
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Blow a lot?
いっぱい吹く?
I'll blow a lot.
いっぱい吹くよ
I got it.
ついちゃった
appear?
見える?
Please lower the camera a little more and show Andal as well.
もう少しカメラ下げてアンダルも見せてください
Okay.
いいよ
Andal looks great.
アンダル超見えるね
I want to see the stars too.
星辺も見たい
I think I'll squirt.
潮吹きしちゃおうかな
I'm totally in it.
全然入っちゃう
I want to see your forehead.
おでこ見たいです
Try giving me your hair.
髪の毛あげてみて
Should I make a ponytail?
ポニーテールにしようかな
Tie your hair quickly.
早く髪結ぶ
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
Let's go
行っちゃお
cormorant.
う
cute.
可愛 い
thank you.
ありがとう
Someone who's already gone.
もう行っちゃった人
Has anyone gone yet?
もう行っちゃった人いる?
Still Minami.
まだみなみ
I still want to go.
まだ行きたい
I want to see some kind of door up.
なんかドアアップ見たい
What does it mean to open to the center?
中央の方まで開いてって何?
Something like this?
こういうこと?
like this?
こう?
It's medium creamy.
中トロトロだよ
How many cups?
何カップ?
It's a nice cup.
いいカップだよ
Quite soft.
結構柔らかい
It's like this.
こんな感じ
Wow, this hurts.
うわ、痛いこれ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくない?
this.
これ
I also like being hurt.
痛くされるのも好きなんだ
I like it.
好きです
I really like it.
めっちゃ好きだよ
This is dangerous.
やばいこれ
Ah, this might be better.
あ、こっちのほうがいいかも
Oh no.
やば
Can I show you the flowers?
お花は見せれますか?
It's like this though.
こんな感じですけど
Can I put my dick in?
チンコ入れていい?
Put it in?
入れて?
I want to put it in.
チンチン入れたい
I wanted to put it in.
入れたくなっちゃった
This feels really good.
マジで気持ちいいこれ
Try serving it with a smile.
笑顔で出してみて
yes.
はい
What can I drink?
何が飲めちゃうの?
replace.
取り替える
I got a little wet,
ちょっとベショベショになっちゃったからさ、
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと待っててね
It's so dirty.
ベッチベチだよもう
There are a lot of Chunan feet.
そ こら中南の足っこだらけ
Wait a minute.
ちょい待ち
I'll be right back.
すぐ戻る
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
I'm running out of towels now.
もうタオルがやばいからさ
headcheese.
ヘッドチーズ
Look, this is terrible.
見て、やばい
It became really heavy.
めっちゃブッシリ重くなっちゃった
Please wait.
待っててね
It's already a little too wet.
ちょっともうベショベショすぎて
terrible.
やばい
I'm home.
ただいま
Yahon.
やっほん
Show me the Sujiman app from Hiratachi.
平立のすじまんアプリ見せて
It's like, when it's closed, nothing really comes out.
なんか、 閉じてると本当何も出てこないんだよね
It's called goo.
グーって言うの
It becomes a perfect fit.
ピ タッとなっちゃう
How old am I?
私はいくつですか?
I'm 20 years old.
20歳だよ
Pitaman.
ピタマン
The close-up is also super cute.
アップも超かわいい
My pussy is a little tired so I think I'll give you a blow job.
ちょっとマンコ疲れちゃったからフェラしようかな
Let's have fun.
よりめしよう
Yorime?
よりめ?
Minami is cute.
みなみかわいいよ
thank you.
ありがとう
Why are you so cute?
なんでそんなにかわいいの?
I love it though.
大好きなんだけど
thank you.
ありがとう
I love Minami too.
みなみも大好き
Let's take a break and try again.
休憩してまたやろう
Give me lots and lots of blowjobs.
いっぱいあるたっぷりのフェラして
Hey, this deed.
ちょっと ね、 このディールド
Do you want to know about this deal again?
このディールド、もう一回知る?
Hard and short chenpo and thin and long chenpo.
硬くて短いチェンポと細くて長いチェンポ
Hard, huh?
硬くて、ん?
I prefer short and hard chenpo.
短くて硬いチェンポの方が好き
Do you like chikumi clips?
チクミクリップ好きなの?
like.
好き
I like it.
好きだよ
Ah, it feels good.
あー、気持ちいい
Crab season.
かにもときじょうい
Would you like to try anal?
アナルしてみる?
Anal because I like anal quite a bit too.
私も結構アナル好きだからアナル
Shall I try it?
入れてみるか
Oh my god, I'm getting so hot.
おー、やばい、なんか熱くなってる
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Let's try it out.
ちょっと試してみよう
Good.
よいしょ
Will this fit?
これ 入るかな?
Good.
よいしょ
Thank you so much for coming.
いっぱい来てくれてありがとう
Will I fit in?
入るかな?
This is big.
おっきいな、これ
Ah, I think I'm about to go in.
あー、入っちゃいそう
Please, tell me you can go.
お願いだから行っていいよって言って
I think if I call you with this, I'm going to go crazy.
これで電話したらマジでめちゃめちゃ行くと思う
Good.
よいしょ
I can't see it.
見えないね
Oh, what is this?
あー、なんだこれ
I can't get in.
入らない
It's really tough though.
めっちゃきついんだけど
This is terrible.
やばいよ
Let it all out inside your anus.
アナルの中にいっぱい出して